? Sometimes we rock and roll ?
? Sometimes we stay at home, and it's just fine ?
思松亦思君
莉亚分享了心情
? This heart's on fire ?
? I am my mother's hen ?
请绕行
Please walk around the other way.
? And left the body in the bed all day ?
-怎么了  -没事
- What happened? ?- Nothing.
只是大厅在为大型派对做准备
They're just getting the lobby ready for the big party.
是年度募捐活动
It's an annual fundraiser.
嘉年华那种吗
Like a carnival?
不  是西装革履的时尚舞会
No, it's a swanky, black-tie ball.
医院大厅也算得上时尚
You think a hospital lobby is swanky?
现在不算  但点上灯  装饰一下
Not yet, but add some lights, a few decorations,
最重要的是要有酒
and, most importantly, alcohol...
那也不过是彩带招摇  气球飘飘
It becomes a streamer- and balloon-infested hospital lobby
有饮料柜台的医院大厅
with a cash bar.
这是慈善舞会
It's for charity.
钱最好用在刀刃上
Better to spend the money for the cause.
其实更糟
Actually, it's worse.
要花钱才能挣到钱
You need to spend money to make money.
我不喜欢派对
I don't like parties.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
全体住院医师都将出席并捐款
All residents will be expected to attend and make a donation.
这位是亚历克斯·朴医生
This is Dr. Alex Park.
他是科利带的住院医师中
He's the last of Coyle's residents
最后一位分到我们团队的医生
to be reassigned to our team.
他们分别是杰瑞德·卡卢医生
Meet doctors Jared Kalu,
克莱尔·布朗医生  肖恩·莫菲医生
Claire Browne, and Shaun Murphy.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
欢迎回归  哥斯达黎加如何
Welcome back. How was Costa Rica?
沙滩很美  猴子很凶
Beaches were awesome. Monkeys were horrible.
小家伙偷了我的新相机和一副...
Little bastards stole my new camera and a pair of --
你多大了
How old are you?
45岁
45.
比梅伦德斯医生还老
That's even older than Dr. Melendez.
莫菲是一位患有自闭症  天赋极高的医生
Dr. Murphy is a talented doctor who has autism,
所以有时会问出不得体的问题
which sometimes causes him to ask inappropriate questions.
没事  不得体的问题或许能发人深省
No worries. Inappropriate questions can be very revealing.
我算是大器晚成
I'm a late bloomer.
朴谦虚了  不像他的作风
Park's being modest, which is very unlike him.
他念医学院之前当了十五年的警察
He was a cop for 15 years before he went to med school.
既然大家都认识了
Now that we all know each other,
雷兹尼克和布朗这周要协助手术
Reznick and Browne have dibs on cases this week.
你们自己选
You make your picks?
-好  -没问题
- Yes. - Definitely.
有卡拉OK吗
Is there karaoke?
现在有请全明星阵容登场
And now, our all-star lineup!
主要活跃于萨斯喀彻温省穆斯乔市之外
Playing center, out of Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan.
斯普里特  停下
Spirit, stop it.
他们没时间陪你胡闹
They don't have time to fool around.
我没在胡闹
I'm not fooling around.
我得记录这一重大事件
I need to document the momentous event.
那起码别搞错了
Then at least get it right.
我来自台湾台北
I'm from Taipei, Taiwan.
纠正
Co-o-orrection!
来自台湾台北
From Taipei, Taiwan --
应该是穆斯乔市郊区的...
which I believe is a suburb of Moose Jaw --
奥德丽·利姆医生
Dr. Audrey Lim!
利姆医生的助手是...
And assisting Dr. Lim are...
我没见过的两位医生
two docs I've never met.
你好
Hello.
我是来自怀俄明州卡斯珀的肖恩·莫菲医生
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy from Casper, Wyoming.
那这位
And...?
我是加利福尼亚州米尔谷的摩根·雷兹尼克医生
Dr. Morgan Reznick, Mill Valley, California.
闪亮登场
Represent!
好了  斯普里特  够了
Okay, Spirit, that's enough.
把你的手机收好
All right, put your phone away,
不然我就没收了
or it becomes my phone.
各位  这位西装男不让我录了
Well, folks, looks like the suits are shuttin' me down.
感谢大家的支持
Thanks for all your support.
爱你们  拜
Love you! Bye!
抱歉  我的朋友们想知道我的最新情况
Sorry, but my friends insist I keep them up to date.
没关系  今天很重要
It's all right. It's a big day.
斯普里特有天生的心脏异位  她一直...
Spirit was born with ectopia cordis. She's been --
怎么没在婴儿时期帮她修复心脏
Why didn't they repair it when she was an infant?
没办法  当时她的肋骨架太小了
They couldn't. Her rib cage was too small.
等她缓慢稳定地长到十四岁后
But after 14 years of slow and steady growth...
是时候送这宝贝回老家了
It's time to put this baby where it belongs.
良     医
第一季    第十五集
这个画面非常神奇
This is an interesting view.
我能看到主动脉弓
I can see the aortic arch.
-莫菲  -没关系
- Murphy. - Oh, it's all right.
我习惯人们好奇的眼光了
I'm used to people being curious.
你肯定很期待
I'm sure you're looking forward
没人再用好奇的眼光看你
to when there's nothing to be curious about.
我真正期待的是...去人多的地方
What I'm really looking forward to is...crowds.
你喜欢人多的地方
You like crowds?
不知道
I don't know.
我从没去过
I've never been in one.
我没法念普通的学校
I can't go to a normal school,
我的父母几乎不让我离开家
and my parents barely ever let me leave our house.
这颗小肿块可能让你心脏停跳  情理之中
Well, when a small bump could stop your heart, it makes sense.
但你还是有很多朋友
But you still have a lot of friends?
对  当然了
Yeah, of course.
只是不能跟他们痛快地玩耍
I mean, I just can't do anything fun with them.
要是不能痛快地玩耍
If you can't do anything fun,
那怎么跟他们交上朋友的
then how did you get them to be your friend?
提醒你一下吧
Well, in case you haven't noticed,
我喜欢聊天
I like to talk.
-对  -而且现在什么事都可以网上操作
- Yes. - ?And, we all do everything online now anyway.
等我出院后第一件事就是
The first thing I'm gonna do when I get out of here
带我的朋友去听音乐会
is take all my friends to a concert.
就是那种最低价的普通门票
Like, general admission, on the floor.
我甚至不在乎是哪支乐队
I don't even care who the band is,
只要那里到处都是人
just as long as the place is packed.
我还要拥抱所有人
And I'm gonna hug everyone.
你从没拥抱过谁吗
You've never hugged anyone?
连父母都没抱过吗
Not even your parents?
亲吻父母  跟朋友击掌庆祝
Kissed by my parents, high-fived by my friends,
但没拥抱过
but, nope, no hugs.
太危险了
It's just too risky.
拥抱让我感觉很束缚
Hugs make me feel trapped.
抱歉
?Sorry.
就快好了
Almost done.
右上腹疼痛
Pain in the upper-right quadrant.
是黄疸
It's jaundice.
胆红素飙升
Bilirubin's off the chart.
没道理啊
That doesn't make sense.
移植术之后他一直恢复得很好
He's been doing so well since the transplant.
今年每次检查都很正常
Yeah, every check-up this year's been perfect.
可能只是暂时的复发
Well, it could just be a temporary flare-up.
我们会加大抗排异药用量
We'll increase his anti-rejection meds
做全肝检查
and do a full liver exam.
到时就会更明确
We'll know more then.
你俩去做检查
You two, do the work-up.
你去找新的肝脏
And you find a new liver.
不该等活检结果吗
Shouldn't we wait for the biopsy result?
我已经知道结果了
Not when I already know what it's gonna say.
得立即给他找新的肝脏
He needs a new liver ASAP.
没那么容易
I mean, that's gonna be hard.
他是O型血
He's Blood Type O.
这几乎不可能
It's gonna be impossible.
最初能找到就已经很幸运了
He's lucky they were able to find the first one.
他最好又能好运
Well, he better get lucky again
因为只有这个办法才能保住他的命
because it's our only way to keep him alive.
完蛋了
We're screwed.
芭芭拉·伯克斯在科苏梅尔岛水肺潜水时
Barbara Boxer got ear barotrauma scuba-diving in Cozumel
造成了耳部气压伤  两周内不能坐飞机
and cannot fly for two weeks,
就是说没人在庆典上做主旨讲话了
which means we don't have a keynote speaker for our gala.
你觉得很好笑吗
You think this is funny?
我只是没见过你焦虑的样子
I've just never seen you anxious,
而且我很怀疑芭芭拉·伯克斯会水肺潜水
and I seriously doubt Barbara Boxer scuba-dives.
只是借口而已
It's just an excuse.
她给我发了在医院的照片
She sent me a picture from the hospital.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
谁都可以伪造照片
Anyone can fake a photograph.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在搜我们伟大的加利福尼亚州参议员
I am doing a search to see if our esteemed senator
在接受采访时有没有  哪怕一次
from the great state of California ever once -- once --
谈到过自己会水肺潜水
talked about scuba-diving in an interview.
真假不重要
It doesn't matter if it's true.
重要的是得找个人替代她
What matters is that we find a replacement.
我需要你帮我安排跟艾登·柯尔特见面
I need you to get me a meeting with Aiden Coulter.
-艾登·柯尔特  -对
- Aiden Coulter? ?- Yes.
我只是有次在奥克兰运动队比赛时坐他旁边而已
What? I sat next to him once at an A's game.
我记得当时
And the story I remember is that
你俩聊了一整晚
you two were talking smack that entire game,
他还在把啤酒洒你身上后
and after he spilled his beer on you
坚持要给你买件新的外套
and insisted on buying you a new jacket,
而你拒绝了
you refused him.
所以他欠你个人情
So he owes you.
安排我跟他见面
Just get me a meeting.
之后的事交给我就好
I'll handle everything from there.
好
Okay.
我会想想办法
I'll see what I can do.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
芭芭拉·伯克斯会水肺潜水吗
没事的
You'll be fine.
你之前做过肝脏活检
You've had liver biopsies before.
而那非常疼
And they've always hurt a lot.
求你了  没其他办法吗
Please, isn't there another way?
埃里克  其他办法就得从脖子下手
Well, the other way, Eric, would going through your neck,
我认为你不会喜欢那样的
and I don't think you'd like that any more.
埃里克  你知道为什么NBA球员
Eric, do you know why NBA players
比赛前都戴耳机吗
all wear headphones before games?
别看他  看着我
Don't look at him. Look at me.
我需要你回答我
I need you to answer me.
为什么NBA球员比赛前戴耳机
Why do NBA players wear headphones before games?
不知道
I don't know.
也许他们喜欢音乐
I guess they like music.
不  他们需要音乐
No, they need music.
音乐帮助他们忘记纷扰
Music helps them forget about everything else
只聚焦于重要的事情
and focus on what's important --
就是比赛
the game.
你最喜欢的球员是谁
Who's your favorite player?
库里
Curry.
好的
Okay.
这是他每次比赛前听的歌曲
This is the song he listens to before every game.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
因为他也是我最爱的球员
Because he's my favorite player, too.
我希望你闭上眼睛集中于此
I want you to close your eyes and focus on this.
就够了
Just this.
好冷
It's cold.
现在确实  但只要你集中精神
Yeah, now it is, but if you stay focused,
很快就不会感觉冷了
pretty soon, it'll stop feeling cold
并开始感觉温暖
and start to feel warm.
当你觉得暖了  你就点下头
When that happens, I want you to nod your head,
你同时会有一些按压以及痛感
and you'll feel some pressure and a small pinch.
如果那样...
What if it does --
那就闭上眼睛集中精神
Then close your eyes and focus.
准备好了吗
You ready?
只需两分钟他就可以手术了
Two minutes and he'll be good to go.
你怎么知道他是个篮球迷
How'd you know he was a basketball fan?
他的鞋子
His shoes.
他没有穿鞋子
He's not wearing any shoes.
鞋在他房间的背包里
Yeah, they're in a backpack in his room.
你翻了他的背包吗
You searched his backpack?
这没有直肠癌那么有攻击性
Well, it's, um, less invasive than a rectal,
而且更多时候还很有用
and most of the time more useful.
斯普里特  保持冷静
Okay, Spirit, just keep still and --
在检查的过程中
And during a few parts of the exam,
我可能需要你屏住呼吸
we may ask you to hold your breath,
但只需要几秒钟
but it'll only be a few seconds.
你都懂的
You got it.
你准备买件燕尾服还是租一件
You gonna buy a tux or rent one?
募捐晚宴要求正规着装
The fundraiser is black tie.
我有一件西服
I have a suit.
是新的
It's new.
我为了面试住院医师买的
I bought it for my resident interviews.
多新都不重要
It doesn't matter how new it is.
它不是燕尾服
It's not a tux.
工作时穿制服使病人心安
Wearing a uniform at work reassures patients.
在派对穿制服没有任何作用
Wearing a uniform at a party does nothing
只会让你很热  并且不舒服
but make you hot and uncomfortable.
这个派对就是工作
This party is work.
去弄一件燕尾服
Get a tux.
别买廉价经销店的劣质款
And not a crappy one from some outlet store.
去买件由专业人士定制的西装  至少花个两千
Get fitted by a pro and spend a minimum of two grand.
你会遇见可以帮助你事业的富豪
You're gonna meet rich people who can help your career,
他们可不愿意帮助邋遢的人
and they're not gonna want to help some slob in a --
我不邋遢
I'm not a slob.
我很干净
No, I am very clean
而且我的衣服从来不起皱
and make sure my clothes are never wrinkled.
这太大了
And it's too big.
她的心脏
Her heart.
和她上次检查相比增大了53%
It's enlarged 53% since her last exam.
她上次检查不过是六个月前
Her last exam was only six months ago.
这样不行
It won't fit.
太大了
Too big.
活组织检查确定了急性细胞排斥反应
The biopsy confirmed acute cellular rejection.
他的免疫抑制剂已经加到最大了  但...
We maximized his immuno-suppressives, but, uh --
我们找到了一个O型肝源
I found one -- a Type-O liver.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
朴和我查过登记中心  并没有什么发现
Park and I checked the registry, and there weren't any.
我在网上发现的
I found it online.
他在几个月前试图直接捐赠
He, uh -- He already tried to make a direct donation a few months ago,
但病人在手术前去世了
but the patient died before the surgery.
我联络了他  这并不简单
I contacted him, which wasn't easy,
但他仍愿意捐赠
but he still wants to be a donor.
太好了
That's amazing.
干得好
Great job.
这里面有什么鬼
What's the catch?
他想成为捐赠者却不在登记中心里
He wants to be a donor, but he's not on the registry?
肯定有鬼
I mean, there's got to be a catch.
他不能进入登记中心
He, uh -- He can't be on the registry
因为他在监狱里
because he is in prison.
由于杀人
For murder.
事实上  七次杀人案
Actually, um, seven murders.
鲍里斯·提拉延是俄罗斯黑手党杀手
Boris Tirayan was a Russian Mafia enforcer
犯了七宗杀人案
convicted of seven murders.
现在想将功补过
Who now wants to make amends.
几个月前他尝试成为捐赠者
He tried to be a donor a few months ago,
但在通过繁文缛节之前  病人去世了
but the patient died before the red tape could be worked out.
但现在...
But now that it has...
有法律禁止囚犯成为捐赠者的吗
Are there any laws against an inmate becoming a donor?
不  但这牵扯到许多责任
No, but there is a ton of liability.
如果他在这里袭击其他人呢
What if he attacks someone here?
他会被监狱守卫看守护送
He'll be guarded by state prison guards on a separate level,
与所有不相关的病人和工作人员隔离开
away from patients and all non-essential staff.
每个人都应有机会改变自己的生活
Everyone deserves the chance to turn their life around.
他想做些好事
The guy wants to do something decent,
我们应该允许
we should let him.
我不认为我们欠一个杀人犯什么
I don't think we owe a murderer anything.
但也许他欠了我们一些东西
But maybe he owes us something.
他亏欠于社会
He has a debt to society.
他会通过捐赠体内器官来偿还
Which he would repay by donating his inner organs.
这不是自讨苦吃吗  一个人想将功补过
Isn't it a slippery slope between a guy who wants to make amends
结果却把监狱系统变成了人体组织仓库
and turning our prison system into a superstore for body parts?
可以拯救孩子生命的自讨苦吃
A slippery slope that saves a child's life.
不可能的
It'll never happen.
他只是想进入医院以便逃跑
He's just trying to get a hospital, where it'll be easier to escape.
你根本不知道他的动机是什么
You have no idea what his motivation is.
我知道他是个骗人的反社会者
I know he's a lying sociopath
不在乎别人只在乎自己
who doesn't care about anyone but himself.
他九年来都是模范囚犯
He's been a model inmate for nine years,
在图书馆指导别的囚犯
tutors other prisoners in the library --
因为他需要别人相信他
Yeah, because he's trying to get someone to trust him,
给他一些甜头  只要他们这样做了
to give him an inch, and as soon as they do --
我们得到了批准
We got approval.
他肯定会借故拖延
He's gonna stall, make excuses,
然后等他找到时机
and when he sees his chance,
就会有人受伤
someone's gonna get hurt.
我觉得值得冒险
I think it's worth taking that chance.
任何不同意的人都可以不参加
Anybody who doesn't agree, feel free to sit this one out.
当你来月经时
When you started menstruating,
增加的雌激素导致肺动脉高压
the increased estrogen caused pulmonary hypertension,
这不是手术的问题
which isn't a surgical issue in itself,
但由于你的非典型血管系统
but along with your atypical vascular system --
你的心脏长得太大了
Your heart's grown too big.
我们会控制你的血压
We will control your blood pressure
这样你会继续发育但你的心脏不会
so that you will keep growing but your heart won't,
等你到十八岁我们就可以...
and then, by the time you're 18, we'll able to --
不
No.
我不想再等了
I'm not waiting any longer.
斯普里特  宝贝  没事的
Spirit, honey, it will be okay.
才不是
No, it won't!
我受不了一直被关在里面
I'm sick of being stuck inside all the time.
我受不了
I'm sick of this!
我不想再发短信  打电话  或者视频了
I don't ever want to text, call, or video chat again.
妈妈  我想和人接触
Mom, I want to be touched.
我想被推挤
I want to be shoved.
我想挨打
I want to be punched.
我根本不在乎  只是...
I don't even care, just --
拜托了
Please.
我想现在就进行手术
I want this surgery now.
我需要它
I need it.
对不起  我们做不到
I'm sorry. We can't.
我们需要弄走所有家具和艺术作品
We need to get rid of all the furniture and artwork.
我可以移走画作  但家具怎么办
I get removing the paintings, but the furniture?
我可不希望监狱守卫在工作时游手好闲
Don't want the prison guards sitting down on the job.
他会被全面限制
He's gonna be in full restraints,
被拷在床上
cuffed to the bed.
这是我们的计划
Well, that's our plan,
但我们也需要为他的计划做准备
but we also need to be prepared for his plan.
我们需要弄走遮光帘
Okay, we need to get rid of the window blinds,
挂帘杆和外套挂钩
curtain rods, jacket hooks,
确定没有任何金属铆钉
and make sure there's no metal rivets
床垫上没有金属圈
or eyelets on the mattress.
他能用金属圈做什么
What's he gonna do with a metal eyelet?
把它从床垫下弄下来然后锉光滑
Tear it off the mattress and file it down
切断你的颈静脉或把它掰成手铐钥匙
to cut your jugular, or bend it into a handcuff key,
或者把它变成电源插头
or shove it into an electric socket
制造火花从而引发火灾
to create a spark and start a fire.
我见过用厕纸肥皂和盐制成的刀
I've seen knives made out of toilet paper, soap, and salt
可以切断一个肥胖男子的股骨
that could amputate a fat guy's femur.
不知道他为何要特意提胖子
Not quite sure he needed the part about the guy being fat.
我在想
So...I've been thinking.
你想一起去募捐晚宴吗
You want to go to the fundraiser together?
不是高校舞会  我们不用携伴参加
It's not a prom. We don't have to bring a date.
是啊  我们不需要
Yeah, we don't have to.
但如果我们想  也可以
But we can, if we want.
基本上每个人都知道我们在约会
Everyone basically knows we're seeing each other,
但是
but still...
我觉得这是个很好的机会
I think it might be a nice opportunity
公开我们的关系
to take our relationship out into the open.
除非你不愿意
Unless you don't want to.
不  这是个好主意
No, it's a good idea.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
你知道我们不用非得这样
Because, you know, we don't have to.
就这么做吧
Yeah. Let's do it.
我们走
Let's go.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没什么  他会好起来的
It's fine. He'll be all right.
我不  我不想要杀人犯的肝脏
No, I won't. I don't want a murderer's liver!
太邪恶了
It's evil!
埃里克  肝脏没有好坏之分
Eric, there's no such thing as a good or bad liver.
它只是...只是个器官
It's just a -- just an organ.
埃里克  这是你唯一的选择了
Eric, this is your only choice.
如果我们不做移植  你会死的
If we don't do the transplant, you will die.
我不想让他成为我的一部分
I don't want him to be a part of me,
永远待在我身体里
inside me forever, all right?
我不管你或者其他人怎么说
I don't care what you or anybody else says, okay?
这是我的身体  我不想接受
It's my body, and I don't want it!
简直荒谬
That's ridiculous.
人格特征不会通过器官移植转移到受体
Personality traits aren't transferred in an organ transplant.
而且这之间毫无关联
It's also irrelevant.
孩子无权同意是否手术
Children don't consent to surgeries --
他们的父母才有权
their parents do.
但如果他不遵医嘱进行抗排异治疗
But if he doesn't cooperate with the anti-rejection regimen,
我们就会浪费本可以救另一个人的肝脏
we could be wasting a liver that could save someone else's life.
提拉延救不了任何人
No one's getting saved by Tirayan.
我找到一位A型捐献者  不完全匹配  但
I found a Type-A donor. It's not a perfect match, but --
他都对一个完全匹配的肝脏有排异反应了
His body's already rejected a perfect match.
血型不匹配的话根本不可能成功
There's no way it can tolerate an incompatible blood type.
不  唯一能救埃里克的方法
No, the only way to save Eric
就是用提拉延的肝脏进行移植
is to do the transplant with Tirayan's liver.
只有这样
That is it.
我们别无选择
We have no other option.
告诉手术室我们需要更多约束带
Let the O.R. know we're gonna need more restraints.
阿尔伯塔省的克林顿·福特医生
Dr. Clinton Ford out of Alberta
研发了一种实验性的可吸收材料
developed an experimental resorbable material.
可以让我们扩展她的胸腔
It would allow us to expand her rib cage
创造足够容纳她心脏的空间
and create room to fit her heart inside.
一片人造胸骨
An artificial sternum.
它可以和患者一起成长
That would actually grow along with the patient.
这个手术是不可逆的
The surgery isn't reversible.
如果不起效
If it doesn't work,
《小儿外科手术学刊》
我们不能将她的心脏挪回原位
we can't just move her heart back to where it was.
但这能让她享受生活
It would allow her to have a life.
她有自己的生活
She has a life,
只要她远离人群  不拥抱任何人
and she'll be healthy as long as she stays out of crowds,
或者不做可能会让自己摔倒的事
doesn't hug anyone,
她会保持健康的
or do anything where she might fall.
我知道你有自闭症
I get you're autistic,
但我也知道即使是你  你也能意识到
but I know even you realize when a patient cries
当一位患者大哭并向墙上扔手机的时候
and throws her phone against the wall,
他们对自己当前的健康状况并不满意
they're not happy with their current health.
你没必要针对他
There's no reason to make this personal.
如果他的医疗决策有偏颇  那就有
There is if his medical judgment is biased.
我看到她不开心
I saw she was upset.
你看到了  但你不理解
You saw it, but you didn't understand it.
你很好胜
You're very competitive.
你是不是试图让利姆医生觉得我有偏见
Are you trying to make Dr. Lim think I'm biased,
还是你想让我丧失自信
or are you trying to undermine my confidence?
我其实是在帮助你和患者
I'm actually trying to help you and the patient.
她想要和人亲近互动
She wants to be able to rub elbows,
你就要去想怎么才能做到
and you need to learn how to trade elbows.
可吸收板材还在实验阶段  有一定风险
The resorbable plate is experimental and risky.
但我的医疗决策是  这值得一试
But my medical judgment is that it's worth it.
一定要让她同意  做好术前准备
Make sure she agrees and then get her prepped.
为什么是我
Why me?
我没什么名气  我对医药一无所知
I'm not famous, I don't know anything about medicine,
在你们的募捐晚宴上让我做致辞
and giving the keynote speech at your fundraiser
比起被啤酒弄脏的夹克  这人情还得太多了
is a steep price to pay for a beer-stained jacket.
你在圣何塞长大
You grew up in San Jose.
虽然你被普林斯顿和麻省理工双双录取
You went to San Jose State
但你却去了圣何塞州立大学
despite being accepted by both Princeton and MIT,
面对芝加哥和明尼安纳波利斯的巨额税收优惠
and you headquartered your company here,
你还是将公司总部设在这里
despite huge tax breaks offered by Chicago and Minneapolis.
而且那是他最喜欢的夹克
And it was his favorite jacket.
当我提出要清理他的夹克时
Well, when I offered to have it cleaned,
他说不用费心  因为他根本不喜欢那件夹克
he said not to bother because he didn't even like the jacket.
-他只是在说客套话  -客套话
- He was being polite. ?- Polite?
我知道你一定没和他比赛过
I take it you've never been to a game with him.
你做了功课  但还不够
You did some homework, but not enough.
我爱这座城市  但我痛恨致辞
I love this city, but I hate giving speeches.
那就不要致辞
So don't give a speech.
给我们讲个故事
Tell us a story.
就像你在青年舞蹈团
Like the one you told at the wrap party
秋季音乐剧庆功宴上讲的那个
at the Youth Dance company's fall musical --
你在巴黎地下墓场迷路的故事
the one where you got lost at the Paris catacombs.
我收回前言
I stand corrected.
你的成功让人鼓舞  艾登
Your success is inspiring, Aiden,
你对这座城市的忠诚也是
as well as your loyalty to this city.
而你如此年轻  非常风趣
And the fact that you're young, apparently very funny --
我同意
I'm in.
其实在艾伦告诉我你为什么
Actually, I was in as soon as Aaron told me
想来和我会面的时候  我就同意了
what you wanted to meet about.
但我很好奇你会如何展开攻势
But I was curious what your attack strategy would be.
你觉得如何
So, how was it?
非常有效
It was very effective.
加州监狱  囚犯
别担心
Now, don't worry.
他已经当了九年的模范囚犯
He's been a model inmate for nine years
并在图书馆为其他狱友进行辅导
and tutors the other prisoners in the library.
在鹈鹕湾州监狱留长指甲很有用啊
Coke nail come in handy up at Pelican Bay?
我做首饰
I make jewelry.
这样更好挑珠子
Helps me pick up the beads.
你有癌症或肝病家族史吗
Is there a history of cancer or liver disease in your family?
我几个月前就回答过了
I went through this a couple of months ago.
你有我的档案
You have my file.
我们需要做自己的检查
We need to do our own exam.
而在先前的档案里没有关于你家人的记录
And there's nothing about your family in previous records.
他们还健在吗
Are they still alive?
对我来说他们已经死了
They're dead to me.
别废话  不然现在就送你回去
Quit stalling, or we'll send you back right now.
我十五岁之后就没和任何家人有联系了
I haven't spoken to anyone in my family since I was 15 years old.
我只知道当年我的父母足够健康
Last I know, uh, both my parents were healthy enough
能每天把我虐打得屁滚尿流
to kick the crap out of me on a daily basis.
还有其他问题吗
Any other questions?
你为什么想这么做
Why do you want to do this?
也许我只是喜欢可爱的护士和难吃的果冻吧
Maybe I just like, uh, cute nurses and bad Jell-o.
-你为什么关心这个  -我们不关心
- Why do you care? - We don't.
只要你乖乖听话照做
As long as you do what you're told.
别担心
Don't worry.
我很擅长遵从命令
I'm very good at following orders.
伯恩斯市议员一定对脸部提拉手术非常满意
Councilman Burns must be very happy with his facelift.
他刚又为募捐晚宴付了一桌的钱
He just bought another table for the fundraiser.
我尽力讨好  但你早就知道了
I aim to please, but you already knew that.
我需要上手术  别装模做样
And I need to get into surgery, so stop being so coy.
怎么了
What's up?
你和伊莎贝尔看上去总是琴瑟和谐
You and Isabel always seem very happy,
能工作生活两不误
able to manage both your professional and personal lives.
谢谢你的夸奖  但还是有点装
I'm flattered you think so, but still a bit coy.
当我去见艾登·柯尔特商讨致辞的事时
When I met with Aiden Coulter about being our keynote,
我觉得我们之间有火花
I thought there was a spark.
现在开始有意思了
Okay, so now we're getting somewhere.
手术可以等几分钟
Surgery can wait a few minutes.
如果我想继续发展是不是不太专业
Is it...unprofessional of me to explore it?
他不是医院员工
He's not a hospital employee,
反而可能是个大金主  而且...
but potentially a significant donor and...
更年轻
younger.
岁数差的不少
Quite a bit.
我不知道  也许我只是在
I don't know, maybe I'm just
臆想根本不存在的东西
imagining something that doesn't even exist.
我不觉得
I doubt that.
你是位迷人  聪颖而有趣的女性
You're an attractive, smart, interesting woman.
我确定当时你们擦出了火花
I'm sure there was a spark.
但你不能和像柯尔特这样的捐助人约会
But you can't date a donor like Coulter.
抱歉
Sorry.
没有规定说不行
There's no actual policy against it.
我不是说规定  而是别人怎么看
I'm not talking policy, I'm talking optics.
你最不想要的就是有人认为
The last thing you want is someone thinking
他的慷慨解囊是一场桃色交易
you'd use sex to get a big donation.
我知道这是双标
It's a double standard, I know,
但这就是现实
but it's the world we live in.
我说了不  我不想要
I said no! I don't want it!
我以为你们已经给他喂药让他安静下来
I thought you gave him something to calm him.
没错  但他非常激动
We did, but he's too agitated.
我要开始静脉注射咪达唑仑了
I'm gonna start him on IV midazolam now.
埃里克  埃里克
Eric -- Eric,
记得先前朴医生说的集中注意力吗
remember what Dr. Park said earlier about focusing?
我知道你能行
I know you can do that.
我们给你戴上之前你用的耳机如何
How about we get those earbuds you had earlier?
不  别碰我
No! Leave me alone!
埃里克  停下
Eric! Stop it.
看着我
Look at me!
别动
Do not move.
你的穿着很有型
You wear very stylish clothes.
谢谢
Thank you.
我猜你是说我不做手术的时候
I assume you mean when I'm not in surgery.
对  你觉得别人认为你是个好医生
Yes. Do you think people believe you're a better doctor
是因为你的衣着吗
because of that?
是有些人这么觉得
Some people.
其他人可能只是觉得
Others probably just think
我喜欢炫耀  人很自大或者是基佬
I'm a show-off or arrogant, gay.
我不管  我是为了我自己
I don't care. I do it for myself.
自己看起来有模有样就感觉很好
You look good, you feel good.
这对你交友有帮助吗
Does it help you make friends?
自我感觉良好对一切都有帮助
Feeling good about yourself helps with everything.
你知道我能去哪里买有型的燕尾服吗
Do you know where I can buy a stylish tuxedo?
我能付两千块
I can pay $2,000.
好吧
Okay.
雷兹尼克医生说
Dr. Reznick says
如果我想认识能对我事业有助力的人
if I want people who matter to help my career,
我需要在募捐晚宴上穿两千块的燕尾服
I need to wear a tuxedo that costs $2,000 to the fundraiser.
你有和格拉斯曼谈过这事吗
Have you talked to Glassman about this?
没有  我现在自己做决定了
No. I make my own decisions now.
莫菲  别人想帮助你的事业
Murphy, people who matter will help your career
是因为他们对你的才能
because they're impressed with your talent
和作为外科医生的潜力印象深刻
and potential as a surgeon.
我可以让你去找我的裁缝
And I could send you to my tailor,
你肯定能花到两千块
where you'll definitely spend two grand.
但我建议你租一件就行
But my advice would be just rent one.
试合身了
Make sure you get fitted by the manager,
花几百元就搞定了
and for a couple-hundred bucks, you'll be fine.
我需要你从十开始倒数
I'm gonna need you to count backwards from 10.
十  九  八...
Ten, nine, eight...
看来你错了
Looks like you were wrong.
我说他会使出浑身解数让我们相信他
I said he'll do anything to convince us to trust him,
让我们放下防备
to let our guard down.
他的眼睛  肿起来了
His eyes, they're swelling up.
还有他的舌头  他过敏了
So is his tongue. He's having an allergic reaction.
停止麻醉
Stop the anaesthesia.
肌肉注射0.5毫克的肾上腺素
Give me 0.5 MGs epinephrine I.M. Now.
我来
I'm on it.
-注射完毕  -他缺氧了
- Epi's in. - He's hypoxic.
我们得给他插管  拿个5.0的管子
We need to intubate. Getting a 5.0 tube.
快
Now!
你对麻醉严重过敏
You had a severe allergic reaction to the anaesthesia.
我们得给你插管  注射类固醇
We had to intubate you and give you steroids.
你们没有做
You didn't do it?
不麻醉的话
We can't operate on you
我们没法在你身上动手术
if you can't breathe under anaesthesia.
你做了能做的一切
You did everything you could.
病人的父母希望你知道
The patient's parents wanted you to know
他们很感激你所做的一切
they're extremely grateful for everything you did.
或是努力去做的一切
Or tried to do.
你们可以再试一次
You can try again.
抱歉  不行
I'm sorry, we can't.
不  你们再试一次
No, you try again.
好吗  再试试
Okay? Try again?
你们再试试
You try again.
再试试
Try again!
冷静点
Calm down!
再试试  再试试
Try again! Try again!
听不懂吗  冷静点
He said calm down! Now!
又是这样  又是这样  对吗
Same old, same old, yeah?
对我来说总是这样
That's the way it's always been for me.
我从没...
Nothing I ever...
他还排在器官资源共享网络的第一位
He's still on the top of the UNOS list,
我们整晚都会一直打电话
and we're gonna be calling and rechecking
复查每个登记表和资料库
every registry and database all night.
我们还有多长时间
How long do we have?
没有新肝脏的话  也许一天
Without a new liver, maybe a day.
你买什么  雨果博斯  阿玛尼
So, what'd you get -- Hugo Boss? Armani?
安德鲁斯医生说我应该租一套
Dr. Andrews said I should just rent one.
你要听他的吗
And you're gonna listen to him?
他是外科手术主任  而且他还懂服装
He's the Chief of Surgery. And he knows about clothes.
如果安德鲁斯有儿子  你觉得他会让他儿子
If Andrews had a son, you think he'd let him
在重要的场合穿着廉价的租赁礼服吗
go to an important event in a cheap rental tux?
他说应以天赋来评判他人
He said people who matter judge people based on their talent.
是  他说的是别人家的孩子
Yeah, that's what he tells someone else's kid.
对于他自己  或他真正尊重的人  他会说实话
To his own, or someone he actually respects, he tells the truth.
切一下这里
Cut here.
你尊重我吗
Do you respect me?
你很聪明  能记住很多信息  但是...
You're smart, able to memorize a ton of information, but...
不  并不
no, not really.
抽吸纵隔
Suction the mediastinum.
你面对一个自己并不尊重的人
You've certainly put a lot of thought
却花了不少心思帮他考虑穿什么去派对
into what someone you claim not to respect wears to a party.
我不尊重他并不代表我不喜欢他
Just because I don't respect him doesn't mean I don't like him.
每个人都觉得穿华丽的衣服不舒服
Everyone's uncomfortable in fancy clothes
讨厌在募捐晚宴上讨好那些权贵
and hates kissing up to bigwigs at a fundraiser.
但是他们会那么做  他们不会畏缩在家
But they do it. They don't cower at home alone.
你用你的自闭症当拐杖
You use your autism as a crutch.
如果你再喜欢他一点  他就该被打成乌眼青了
Okay, I think if you liked him any more, he'd have a black eye.
确保那边已经搞定  主动脉没有缠绕在一起
Make sure we're clear on that side and the aorta isn't kinked.
-主动脉没有缠绕在一起  -很好
- The aorta isn't kinked. - Good.
关键的时刻到了
Now for the moment of truth.
放进去
Position the plate.
很合适
Perfect fit.
搞什么
What the hell?
你做了什么
What'd you do?
我什么都感觉不到
I don't feel nothing.
不  别碰他
No, don't touch him.
如果他控制不了他的膀胱...
If he can't control his bladder...
他可以控制自己
He can control himself just fine.
想的挺美  但是假期结束
Nice try, but the vacation's over.
站起来
Stand up.
先再检查一遍他的手铐
Re-check his cuffs first.
你去换衣服  然后我们就走
You're getting changed, and we're going.
就这么带他走吧
Just take him like he is.
我才不会就这么
I'm not gonna get stuck in the van
和他在车里待三个小时
for the next three hours with him like that.
小心他的手  小心他的手
Watch his hands! Watch his hands!
放下枪
Put the gun down now!
你开枪  他死
You shoot me, he dies.
谁都不会开枪的
Now, no one is shooting anyone.
大家都保持冷静
Everyone stay calm.
给他空间
Give him space.
你做了好事  鲍里斯
You did something good, Boris.
别毁了它
Don't ruin it now.
我什么都没做  不是吗
I did nothing, yeah?
我什么都没做成
I accomplished nothing!
接下来发生什么完全取决于你
Whatever happens next is completely in your control.
你有掌控权  但并不是无限制的
You have power, but it's not unlimited.
你跑不了
You're not gonna escape,
你是不可能走出这里的
you're not just walking out of here.
但是可以做一些让步
But there are things, concessions,
让你的生活更好一些
that could make your life better.
所以我们聊聊吧
So let's just take our time and talk.
不着急
There's no rush.
你想要什么  鲍里斯
What do you want, Boris?
你真正想要什么
What do you really want?
我不想让任何人救我
I don't want anyone to help me.
无论你们把那些叫做什么  那些抢救措施
Whatever you call it, these life-saving measures.
我  不要
I -- No.
不要
No.
不要那么做
Do not do it.
别听她的  是你的选择
Don't listen to her. It's your choice.
你想怎么做都可以
You do what you want.
是啊
Yeah.
鲍里斯  不要
Boris, no!
快走  快  快
Let's go! Let's go! Move! Move!
梅伦德斯在路上
Melendez is en route.
好了  准备好了吗  走
All right, ready? Let's go.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
立刻呼叫泌尿外科和心胸外科
Page urology and cardio-thoracic stat.
他死了  他签署了器官捐献志愿书
He's dead and he has a donor card.
我们要取走他所有能捐献的东西
We're gonna take everything he can donate.
年度盛典
BGM: Everyday by Nvdes
? Our love was hard to maintain, so we broke it ?
? But your smile reminds me that I cannot lose all of you ?
? So can we can we laugh about being crazy? ?
感谢你
Thank you so much.
你的致辞很完美
Your speech was perfect.
而且很幽默
And hilarious.
太客气了
You're very welcome.
我很感谢有这个机会可以改变我的名声
And I appreciate the opportunity to help change my rep.
你还有名声
You have a rep?
工作狂  不玩乐
All work and no play.
我现在正努力作出改变
Something I'm working on changing.
你的名声还是生活方式
Your rep or your lifestyle?
我得减小压力  获得更多乐趣
I need less stress and more fun.
你想哪天一起去打高尔夫吗
Would you like to play golf sometime?
在真正的球场上打
On a real course with actual grass.
当然
Absolutely.
想跳舞吗
Would you like to dance?
乐意之至
I'd love to.
好了  走吧
All right, let's go.
? Like it's true ?
? So can we laugh about being crazy? ?
我们得立刻给埃里克做好准备
We need to get Eric prepped right away.
发生什么了  你们找到新的肝脏捐赠者了吗
What's happening? Did you find a new liver donor?
实际上  还是同一个人
Actually, it's -- it's the same one.
情况有变
The circumstances have changed.
真令人难以置信
This is incredible.
不  我不想要
No, I don't want it.
埃里克  当捐赠者发现
Eric, when the donor found out
他不能做手术帮助你
that he couldn't do the surgery to help you,
他特别伤心
he became incredibly sad
因为他更想你活着
because he wanted you to live more than he wanted to live.
他结束了自己的生命  为了让你可以移植肝脏
He ended his life so that you could have his liver.
他知道自己做过一些坏事
He -- He knew he'd done some bad things,
我想这是他认为的唯一的弥补方法
and I think that this was the only way he knew how to make amends.
我觉得我们应该努力帮帮他
I think we should try and help him.
你觉得你可以那么做吗...
Do you think you can do that --
帮助他人  做好事
help someone do something good?
好吧
Yeah.
一切都很不错的样子
Everything looks good good.
记得深呼吸
Remember to take deep breaths
这样你就不会有肺部的并发症
so you don't develop any lung complications,
当然  还有在接下来的几周
and, obviously, avoid lifting anything too heavy
要避免提重物
for the next few weeks.
我...
I...
怎么了  宝贝
What, honey?
我想抱抱
I want a hug.
BGM: Smooth Sailin' by Leon Bridges
? Over the horizon, she's smooth sailin' ?
? These concrete seas ?
? Now she's headed ?
你看起来像个百万富翁
You look like a million bucks.
不  这身2368元
No, it cost $2,368.
很值
Well, it was worth every penny.
很好的投资
Good investment.
很高兴看到你犒劳你自己了
Glad to see you're treating yourself.
这是你应得的
You deserve it.
你的裙子多少钱
How much did you dress cost?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
你知道吗  这种晚宴上
And just so you know, that's not the best question
不适合提这种问题
for an event like this.
为什么
Why not?
不知道  就是不太行
I don't know. It just isn't.
好吧
Okay.
我能请你喝一杯吗
Can I buy you a drink?
我再也不喜欢龙舌兰了
I don't like tequila anymore.
喝了就想吐
It makes me vomit.
好吧  这里也有别的酒
Well, okay. They have other choices.
来杯葡萄酒或苏打水吗
A glass of wine or a soda?
不要  谢谢
No, thank you.
那边有个律所合伙人
that's a partner at a firm
上个月帮我们做过一些志愿法律服务
that did some pro bono work for us last month,
我得去感谢他一下
so I have to go thank him.
好  再见
Okay. Bye.
? I won't wear you down ?
? No, honey, I won't ?
? Wear you down ?
? She's smooth ?
你好
Hello.
? Smooth sailin' ?
? She's smooth ?
? Smooooth, darling ?
你在这里啊
There you are.
打扮得不错
And nicely done.
有了这身打扮
You got the look.
就一定要好好利用
Now you got to put it to use.
你还有任务呢
There's work to do.
跟人交流
Mingle.
好的
Okay.
我看到你了  陈医生
I see you, Dr. Chen.
她是梅奥医学中心的利文顿协会负责人
She runs the Rivington Fellowship at the Mayo Clinic.
不知道谁把她带来的
I wonder who brought her here.
我不知道
I don't know.
交流
Mingle.
你还是觉得人是无法改变的吗
You still think people can't change?
反正他没变
He didn't.
他就是一个为财害命的凶手
He's an assassin who murdered people for money.
今天只不过是又一次的冷血谋杀
Today was just one more cold-blooded killing.
你帮助他牺牲了自己的生命
You helped him sacrifice his life
从而让他可以去救其他人
so that he could save someone else.
我并不赞成你的做法
I am not a fan of what you did,
即便这证明了...
even if it did prove --
他并没有什么牺牲
He didn't sacrifice anything.
他死了很久了
He died a long time ago.
他的帮派早就散了
His crew is probably gone.
在监狱里  他什么都不是
In prison, he was a nobody.
现在呢  他像个英雄一样
And now? He lives on as a hero
对埃里克的家人  媒体和你而言皆是如此
to Eric's family, to the press, to you.
黄疸病情有所好转
Jaundice is improving.
水肿也在消散
Edema's resolving, too.
各项体征都还不错
His vitals look good.
今晚挺成功的
It's been great night.
有另外三个人的生命也得到了拯救
Three other lives were saved, as well.
他父母知道他做的事吗
Does his parents know what he did?
我想送他们一张卡片
I want to send them a card.
我知道他们可能会很伤心  但是...
I know they're gonna be sad, but...
我想告诉他们  我会好好照顾他们儿子的肝脏
I want to tell them I'll take good care of their son's liver.
我觉得这个想法非常好
I think that's a great idea.
真是不错
This is impressive.
BGM: Good Time by Earl St. Clair
有点像高中舞会  不过大家没长青春痘
It's kind of like prom, but without the acne.
还有一个上周播放过「米高梅大酒店」的DJ
And with a DJ that played the MGM Grand last week.
能有幸请你跳支舞吗
Would you do me the honor?
? On the floor ?
? I bet you think you look cool ?
真有型
Classy.
我现在处于最佳状态而已
I brought my A-game.
? They don't play no more slow cuts ?
? Everything is turned up ?
? I bet you think you look cool ?
? Look cool ?
? I'm not the one to rain on parades ?
? But you in the club in some shades ?
? What is goin' on now, a day ?
? Now a day ?
? This is why I stay in the house ?
? I'm better off parked on the couch ?
-拍个照吧  -你真漂亮
- Take a picture. - Ooh, you look great!
? When I go out, go out ?
? Put on my Sunday best and show out (Show out) ?
? I just wanna have a good time (Good time, good time) ?
? I just wanna have a good time ?
? Oh, yeah ?
刚开始这会儿最难熬
The first little while is the hardest,
之后就能进行下一步了
and then you move on.
你就从不这样
You never did.
这倒是真的
Well, that's true.
但这并不意味着你也不用
Doesn't mean you don't have to.
也许吧
Maybe.
谢谢
Thank you.
你要怎么做  枯坐着自怨自艾吗
Well, what are you gonna do? Are you gonna sit around and mope?
至少试一下嘛
At least try.
我要怎么做
How do I do that?
我不知道
I don't know. ?
如果我知道我自己早就做了
If I knew, I would have done it.
我们跳舞吧
Let's dance.
好吧  这样挺好的
Okay. That would be lovely.
别害羞  你伤害不了我
Don't be shy. You can't hurt me.
看  我有个仿生胸骨
Look! I have a bionic sternum!
你闻起来很香  珍妮
Ooh, you smell good, Jenny.
这是什么味  草莓吗
What is that -- strawberry?
草莓香芒  是唇彩的味道
Strawberry mango. It comes with a lip gloss.
我从商场里买的
I got it at the mall.
我们可以一起逛商场
We can go together!
就这么说定了
It's a plan!
我们都去
Let's all go!
话说  我们自拍一个吧
You know what, let's take a selfie.
-好  -好
- Yeah. - Yeah.
好主意  过来
That's a great idea. Bring it in.
大家都过来  靠近一点
Bring it in, guys! Closer!
-和平  -茄子
- Peace sign! - Cheese!
-耶  -好了
- Yay! - Okay.
太好玩了
That was so funny.
BGM: Severing Ties (Avec Sans Remix) by Young Summer
? This ghost of mine, I hope that it follows you ?
BGM: Touch by Shura
好吧
Okay.
? There's a love between us still ?
还记得这首歌吗
Remember this?
我应该记得吗
Should I?
你真的不记得了
You really don't remember?
不记得
No.
怎么了
What's wrong?
这是我们第一次在医院值夜班时放的歌
It's the song that played during our first overnight at the hospital.
? I wanna touch you, but I'm too late ?
我们伴着这首歌第一次接吻
We had our first kiss to this song.
? I wanna touch you, but there's history ?
抱歉  今天真是太累了
I'm sorry. It's been a long day.
是啊
Yeah.
杰瑞德  这并不能说明什么
Jared, it doesn't mean anything.
不  这很有什么
Yeah, it does.
? There's a love between us still ?
我爱你  克莱尔
I love you, Claire.
你却从未爱过我
You never loved me.
我本以为总有一天你会有所改变  但...
Now, I thought that maybe someday that would change, but...
实际上并不会
it won't.
? But I know I'm out of my mind ?
再见  克莱尔
Bye, Claire.
? There's a love between us still ?
? But something's changed, and I don't know why ?
? Never felt so close, but now I know it's over ?
? And all I wanna do is go home with you ?
BGM: Surround Me by Leon
? The lights go down ?
? I want you around me ?
? Don't overthink it ?
? Just finish up your drink ?
? And surround me ?
我收到140份会员申请
I have 140 applications for fellows,
? Surround me ?
但是没有一个人知道怎么写...
not one of them has a clue how to write an --
你好
Hello.
我是肖恩·莫菲医生
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy.
我是本院的住院医师
I'm a resident here.
我是杰克·利维医生  肿瘤外科
I'm Dr. Jake Levy, surgical oncology.
托比·杨  病理科
Toby Yang, pathology.
梅·柯蒂斯  骨科
May Curtis, ortho.
好的
Okay.
很显然  我错了
Apparently I was wrong.
我告诉莫菲医生最好租个燕尾服
I told Dr. Murphy he'd be fine renting a tuxedo.
显然他没听我的话
Clearly, he chose not to listen.
-对不起  -不用  你看起来很帅
- ?I'm sorry. - Don't be. You look fantastic.
这是什么牌子  阿玛尼
What is it -- Armani?
是的  花了...
Yes, it cost --
不管你花了多少钱  都很值
Well, whatever you paid for it, it was worth.
高尔夫球赛比得如何  杰克
How's the golf game, Jake?
一如往常
Same as always.
我知道球赛近况
I know how that is.
你也玩高尔夫吗  莫菲
You play golf, Murphy?
我玩过  但我不喜欢
I have, but I don't like it.
我们都不喜欢
None -- None of us do.
老话说得好  「高尔夫就是变质的散步」
You know what they say -- "Golf is a good walk spoiled."
? Surround me ?
没错
Yes.
? So don't let me go ?
? No, don't let me go ?
? Surround me ?